Okay, so the set timeout function is
really helpful because it allows us to
delay the execution of a function for a
set amount of time. For example, if I
had a function here
um called log and inside I console.log
hello world. If I call this function
inside of my script tag, it'll run
immediately. So if I save this and I
come over to my website, you can see
hello world loads as soon as the page
loads. It's nearly instantaneously on
the page. But sometimes it's really
helpful to be able to delay execution of
a function. So if you want to delay the
execution of a function, you can do
something. You can use a function called
set timeout. So if I say set timeout,
this function takes in two things. It
takes in a function to call after a set
time and it takes the amount of time
that you want to time out. that's given
in milliseconds. So for example, if I
want to call my log function, I'll pass
in the log function as the first
parameter and then 30,00 milliseconds as
the second parameter and that will give
us 3 seconds and then it will log. So if
we come over here and reload one, two,
three, there it is. And so we
successfully were able to pause function
a function from running for a set amount
of